<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>This Movie Year</title>
    <description></description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 14:37:47 -0600</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2016 14:37:47 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.0.1</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Godfather Night</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Morbi interdum mollis sapien. Sed ac risus. Phasellus lacinia, magna a ullamcorper laoreet, lectus arcu pulvinar risus, vitae facilisis libero dolor a purus. Sed vel lacus. Mauris nibh felis, adipiscing varius, adipiscing in, lacinia vel, tellus. Suspendisse ac urna. Etiam pellentesque mauris ut lectus. Nunc tellus ante, mattis eget, gravida vitae, ultricies ac, leo. Integer leo pede, ornare a, lacinia eu, vulputate vel, nisl.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Suspendisse mauris. Fusce accumsan mollis eros. Pellentesque a diam sit amet mi ullamcorper vehicula. Integer adipiscing risus a sem. Nullam quis massa sit amet nibh viverra malesuada. Nunc sem lacus, accumsan quis, faucibus non, congue vel, arcu. Ut scelerisque hendrerit tellus. Integer sagittis. Vivamus a mauris eget arcu gravida tristique. Nunc iaculis mi in ante. Vivamus imperdiet nibh feugiat est.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/article/the-godfather-night.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/article/the-godfather-night.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>article</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Cag3d: The Nic Cage Marathon</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;If you plan on watching 5 back to back mystery Nicolas Cage movies, SIGN ME UP. I’m not saying this ironically either. I’d easily put him in my top 10 favorites. I mean lets be real the guy can take any character he plays and somehow put the craziest accent, weirdest twist, and most outrageous outburts; and somehow it all fits in perfectly…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img style=&quot;float: left; width: 200px; height: auto; margin-right: 10px;&quot; src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/nic_salvador.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So when I heard about the &lt;a href=&quot;https://drafthouse.com&quot;&gt;Alamo Drafthouse&lt;/a&gt; playing a 5 mystery movie Nic Cage marathon… C’mon… You know what happened. So here we go.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The idea going in was, well, this was the 3rd one they had done (HOW I JUST FOUND OUT I’UNNO) and they play 5 movies starring Cage; but they don’t tell anyone what those movies are going to be. So you’re in for a surprise, obviously.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also, if you don’t know anything about the Drafthouse theaters. They’re basically a safe haven for us movie goers. Great food, great showings, drinks, etc etc etc. Also they do these 30 minute preshow clips that are always on point.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And real quick, I’m going to give these movies each a 1-5 star rating, not the traditional 3 star rating from TMY. I just want to preface this with, yes you should watch all these 5 movies in this order non stop back to back. But also I will give you some realistic expectations going on, I can’t just say 3 star to them all. 3 stars goes to the whole event…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;but-lets-just-dive-into-the-marathon-shall-we&quot;&gt;But let’s just dive into the marathon shall we&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I give you, the 5 mystery movie line up:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/drive_angry.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;drive-angry&quot;&gt;Drive Angry&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-vengeful-father-escapes-from-hell-and-chases-after-the-men-who-killed-his-daughter-and-kidnapped-his-granddaughter&quot;&gt;A vengeful father escapes from hell and chases after the men who killed his daughter and kidnapped his granddaughter.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I can’t stand behind how well of an opener this movie is to a Nic Cage Marathon. For those of you who haven’t watched this movie its basically… Imagine if someone told Cage “Hey man for the next whatever hours or days… you can’t die or anything or whatever, have fun.” And then Cage OF COURSE, just goes fucking ballistic. I mean theres a story here of him trying to save his granddaughter and some other shit from some evil cult. BUT LOOK IT SAYS HE ESCAPES HELL.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;He says the most off the wall, most extreme shit you could think of. It’s seriously one of the best movies I’ve ever had the experience of watching.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Also he kills like 8 people, WHILE HAVING SEX. So there’s that to look forward to. This movie has it all, it’s got action, adventure, love, drama, thriller. AND William Fichtner fucking casually walking out of a flying rolling semi gas tanker onto the top of a stationary cop car… ARE YOU KIDDING ME&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/moonstruck.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;moonstruck&quot;&gt;Moonstruck&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;loretta-castorini-a-book-keeper-from-brooklyn-new-york-finds-herself-in-a-difficult-situation-when-she-falls-for-the-brother-of-the-man-she-has-agreed-to-marry&quot;&gt;Loretta Castorini, a book keeper from Brooklyn, New York, finds herself in a difficult situation when she falls for the brother of the man she has agreed to marry.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay, turning this thing around 180 degrees. Here we go. Keeping things on earth for this movie. If there was another movie following Drive Angry that was so off the wall this could have gone sideways. This was necessary to keep things grounded.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now this is a movie you’re going to be 20 minutes in thinking “Did I start the right movie? Wheres Cage?”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I promise you he’s in this movie. And his intro couldn’t have been better to be honest. He really goes off the wall the moment you see him. I mean he’s upset about his hand and losing his girl and all that, but he blames his brother, that’s random as fuck lets be real. However, thinking about it this way. He wouldn’t have met Cher the way he did if he didn’t have this bad blood between brothers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a delightfully uplifting movie. It’s got that late 80s humor and some really over the top dramatic scenes I’d say. Definitely a rom com for the books.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/matchstick_men.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;matchstick-men&quot;&gt;Matchstick Men&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-phobic-con-artist-and-his-protg-are-on-the-verge-of-pulling-off-a-lucrative-swindle-when-the-formers-teenage-daughter-arrives-unexpectedly&quot;&gt;A phobic con artist and his protégé are on the verge of pulling off a lucrative swindle when the former’s teenage daughter arrives unexpectedly.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You know I think this movie was only about 75% of the way written, then they casted Cage and he comes in and gives this off the wall OCD behavior character and Scott just looked up and said. “Yep, thats fuckin’ it man.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quick back story here, I LOVE RIDLEY SCOTT. I mean Blade Runner is still my all time favorite. That guy can direct. So seeing this movie come up next was a nice reminder of why I’m here in the first place. It’s one of those Ridley Scott films you watch and you really like. But it’s not one you’ll watch that often, it just never comes to mind!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And thats why this one is perfect for the midway point in your marathon. You probably haven’t seen this one in a long time, or you haven’t seen it at all.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So it’ll be a delightful refresher for you to watch and enjoy, its entertaining, its got a nice twist and ultimately it ends just as fucking weird as the other two movies you just watched. We’ll get to that in a sec though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/snake_eyes.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;snake-eyes&quot;&gt;Snake Eyes&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-shady-police-detective-finds-himself-in-the-middle-of-a-murder-conspiracy-at-an-important-boxing-match-in-an-atlantic-city-casino&quot;&gt;A shady police detective finds himself in the middle of a murder conspiracy at an important boxing match in an Atlantic City casino.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You got Snake Eyes man! Holy shit I couldn’t hold back my excitement when this one started playing. I love Gary Sinise and he plays the perfect good/bad guy. Oh hey, so does Cage!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is two good guys who aren’t really all that good, battling it out on who’s right and who’s wrong. Who knew a boxing match would be the place to grow, or lose, a conscious. Also I’m pretty sure Cage got to pick out this fucking bad ass hell attire he’s rocking at the start.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But in all seriousness this is just another testament to the EXTREME range that Cage can rock. I mean just last movie he was twitching every 5 seconds and stuttering, etc. Method actors really just get me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This movie, like in the spirit of this list, also ends in just as weird of a set up as all the others. With Cage about to pop off to jail for his shit before the whole movie even started! Just goes to show you man, sometimes you just can’t dodge a bullet.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;col-md-4&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/article_assets/cag3d/wicker_man.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;wicker-man&quot;&gt;Wicker Man&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;i class=&quot;fa fa-star&quot;&gt;&lt;/i&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;a-sheriff-investigating-the-disappearance-of-a-young-girl-from-a-small-island-discovers-theres-a-larger-mystery-to-solve-among-the-islands-secretive-neo-pagan-community&quot;&gt;A sheriff investigating the disappearance of a young girl from a small island discovers there’s a larger mystery to solve among the island’s secretive, neo-pagan community.&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So here’s a fun fact for you guys. From Cage himself, his most favorite movie he likes to watch of himself. Would just happen to be none other than one of my not so favorites…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Overall I do like this movie. I honestly do agree with Nic it’s probably one of his better movies when it comes to his skill of acting. The whole movie I feel like you have to trudge through though.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a bit slow moving, the plot and the story are there, the acting is solid. It just lags behind when it comes to either being a thriller, mystery, or horror movie. It just doesn’t quite hit any of those in my opinion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But, it’s a perfect way to end a night of movies ending in a bad spot for our main hero as he’s burned alive in a giant Burning Man style ritual.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;so-there-we-have-it&quot;&gt;So there we have it&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;That will bring us to an end on this delightful marathon. I hope you sit down one rainy Saturday with your loved ones and enjoy what I too witnessed. Also keep in mind, next year there might be a nice surprise in the form of the almighty himself making a presence. We shall see.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jan 2016 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/article/cag3d.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/article/cag3d.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>article</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Revenant</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/adventure/drama/thriller/the-revenant.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/adventure/drama/thriller/the-revenant.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Adventure</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
        <category>Thriller</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Hateful Eight</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 25 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/thriller/western/drama/mystery/the-hateful-eight.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/thriller/western/drama/mystery/the-hateful-eight.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Thriller</category>
        
        <category>Western</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
        <category>Mystery</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Big Short</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/the-big-short.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/the-big-short.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Creed</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2015 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/creed.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/creed.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Spectre</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 26 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/action/adventure/thriller/spectre.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/action/adventure/thriller/spectre.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Action</category>
        
        <category>Adventure</category>
        
        <category>Thriller</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Last Witch Hunter</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 23 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/fantasy/action/adventure/the-last-witch-hunter.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/fantasy/action/adventure/the-last-witch-hunter.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Fantasy</category>
        
        <category>Action</category>
        
        <category>Adventure</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Crimson Peak</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/romance/horror/thriller/mystery/fantasy/crimson-peak.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/drama/romance/horror/thriller/mystery/fantasy/crimson-peak.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
        <category>Romance</category>
        
        <category>Horror</category>
        
        <category>Thriller</category>
        
        <category>Mystery</category>
        
        <category>Fantasy</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Beasts of No Nation</title>
        <description>
</description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/movie/war/drama/beasts-of-no-nation.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/movie/war/drama/beasts-of-no-nation.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>movie</category>
        
        <category>War</category>
        
        <category>Drama</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
